The key to frog farming
is surviving the fattening stage
One small mistake
and over half can die
It all comes down to this
Water quality, temperature, and feed
are all critical
Their weight is on target
They're healthy
and have put on enough weight
The key fattening stage is over
Now we wait until fall to harvest the oil
Lewes
With 50,000 bucks
you could've gone out and had a blast
But you insisted on copying me
Now you're drowning in debt
and working yourself to death
It's alright
I did the same work for you before
Working for myself
is actually easier
I can rest when I'm tired
No one will get annoyed
and force me to work
I was doing it for your own good
You see
you need to know your limits
You're not cut out for raising forest frogs
Stop dreaming of getting rich overnight
Go back to farming the fields
That's better than anything
By the way
I invited a few buyers for dinner tomorrow
Bring my sister and your parents along
No, thanks
I can't leave the farm
Even with my massive farm
I didn't say I couldn't leave
You only have a few frogs here
Are you disrespecting me
Fine, I'll go
That's more like it
Tomorrow at noon
at the best hotel in town, Prosperity Hotel
Don't be late
He just wants to use me
to show off his success
Don't be late
Enjoy it while you can
Once this batch of forest frogs
starts yielding oil
you won't be
laughing anymore